[{"id":273,"question":"Which \u2018meta box\u2019 is not hidden by default on Post and Page screens?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Featured Image is the meta box that is not hidden by default on Post and Page screens.","answer_b":"Featured Image is the child box that is hidden by default on Post and Page screens.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":945,"question":"Which of the following commands would show you the status of a Kubernetes deployment?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl rollout stats deployment\/Deployment","answer_b":"kubectl rollout status deployment\/Deployment","answer_c":"kubectl rollout log deployment\/Deployment","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":670,"question":"Which is the invalid file name in UNIX?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"LINUX","answer_b":"a.widows","answer_c":"bill .gates","answer_d":"All of the above","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":951,"question":"Which statement is true for Replica set?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Replica set is considered as a substitute to the replication controller. The prime function of replica set is to assure the number of pod replicas running.","answer_b":"Replica set is considered as the legacy replication controller. The prime function of replica set is to remove the number of pod replicas running.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":990,"question":"What is the correct JavaScript syntax for opening a new window called \"w2\" ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"w2 = window.new(\"http:\/\/www.w3schools.com\");","answer_b":"w2 = window.open(\"http:\/\/www.w3schools.com\");","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":842,"question":"Following Docker command: docker commit -m \"My first update\" container_ID user_name\/repository_name  is used to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Activate default VM machine","answer_b":"Commit changes done in a Docker image","answer_c":"Build an image","answer_d":"Access a running container","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":519,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a hyperlink?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<a href=\"http:\/\/mcqsets.com\">MCQ Sets Quiz<\/a>","answer_b":"<http:\/\/mcqsets.com<\/a>","answer_c":"<a name=\"http:\/\/mcqsets.com\">MCQ Sets Quiz<\/a>","answer_d":"url=\"http:\/\/mcqsets.com\">MCQ Sets Quiz","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":68,"question":"What is the correct way to include the file \"time.inc\" ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<?php include file=\"time.inc\"; ?>","answer_b":"<?php include:\"time.inc\"; ?>","answer_c":"<?php include \"time.inc\"; ?>","answer_d":"<!-- include file=\"time.inc\" -->","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":861,"question":"How to show the logs of the docker container with contained id mentioned in the command.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$ docker logs 09ca6feb6efc","answer_b":"$ docker ---logs 09ca6feb6efc","answer_c":"$ docker log 09ca6feb6efc","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":265,"question":"Where is WordPress content stored?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"WordPress stores it's content in a MySQL database on the server.","answer_b":"WordPress stores it's content in the wp-content folder","answer_c":"WordPress stores it's content in a MySQL database on the server.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1078,"question":"If you see a directory with the following permissions `drwxrwxrxt`, would you be able to remove it?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Only the owner of the folder can remove this folder","answer_b":"Yes, we can remove it from any user","answer_c":"We can remove it with the root user","answer_d":"We can remove it only using the root user","answer_e":"No, this folder can't be remove.","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":534,"question":"The _____ character tells browsers to stop tagging the text","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"?","answer_b":">","answer_c":"%","answer_d":"\/","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":485,"question":"Which HTML element is used to define the description Data?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<dt>","answer_b":"<dl>","answer_c":"<li>","answer_d":"<dd>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":1040,"question":"You can also get the Ansible documentation directly via your terminal by using:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ansible-doc","answer_b":"ansible --doc","answer_c":"ansible -d","answer_d":"ansible-documentation","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":131,"question":"Which character is used to indicate an end tag?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/","answer_b":"<","answer_c":"*","answer_d":"^","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":996,"question":"What will the following code return: Boolean(10 > 9)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"true","answer_b":"NaN","answer_c":"false","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":881,"question":"Which are the default networks in Docker?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The default networks in Docker include bridge, host and none.","answer_b":"The default networks in Docker include rope, pin and halt.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":145,"question":"Block elements are normally displayed without starting a new line.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1032,"question":"How to list all of your services in Docker swarm?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"docker ls service","answer_b":"docker service ls","answer_c":"docker service ps","answer_d":"docker get service","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":953,"question":"Egress is incorrectly speed Ingress","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"false","answer_b":"true","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"}]
